gamereplays.org 2019-09-25

# GameReplays.org Privacy Policy - GameReplays.org

##  GameReplays Privacy Policy

_**Privacy Policy for GameReplays.org Limited**_

**GameReplays.org** is committed to protecting your privacy when you use our on-line services ("Services"). In this policy we explain how and why we collect your information, what we do with it and what controls you have over our use of it.

From time to time we add or change functions, features or products to our Web Sites or add or change Services. This, and our commitment to protecting the privacy of your personal information, may result in periodic changes to this Privacy Policy. As a result, please remember to refer back to this Privacy Policy regularly to review any amendments. 

Any questions regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed to  or to a Global Admin via the Private Messaging system.

**Your acceptance of these Privacy Statement terms**

By using any of the sites within our web site network ("Web Sites") or our Services, you unconditionally agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

**What data do we collect and how do we use it?**

**GameReplays.org** collects and processes information about you in order to:  
(i) identify you each time you visit a Web Site or wish to have a Service provided;   
(ii) process orders or applications submitted by you;   
(iii) improve our Services and Web Sites   
(iv) Customise your experience, for example, provide advertisements that we think are relevant to you and which support any specific requests for information you may make through keyword searches;   
(v) carry out research on the demographics, interests and behaviour of all of our customers; and   
(vi) send you information we think you may find useful, including information about new GameReplays.org products and services.

You may be asked, either when you register with us, or at other times, for information about yourself, such as your name, e-mail address, postal address and telephone number. You may also be asked to share with us your interests, hobbies and preferences. In addition, when you order certain goods or services from our Web Sites, we will need to know your credit/payment card number and expiration date.

 _You are under no obligation to provide this information_

, but if you don't then we may not be able to provide you with certain services or personalise your experience and tailor our Services for you (for example, tell you about special offers on things you are interested in).

**Log files/IP addresses**

When you visit our Web Sites, we automatically log your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet) which is automatically recognised by our web server. We use IP addresses to help us administer our Web Sites and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information although we reserve the right to link your IP address(es) to your registered username and email address for the purposes of monitoring abuse of the site rules, and to ban certain IP addresses from using our Web Sites.

**Non personal information**

We may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use or the site from which you linked to our Web Sites. You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on our Web Sites. We may from time to time supply the owners or operators of third party sites from which it is possible to link to our Web Sites with information relating to the number of users linking to our Web Sites from their sites. You cannot be identified from this information.

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information that a Web Site transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a Web Site if you do so. Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the web.

An exception to this is that our third party advertising providers may use cookies for the purposes of the better targeting of advertisements on **GameReplays.org** and other websites not in the **GameReplays.org** network. **GameReplays.org** does not control or have access to or control of cookies placed by third parties.

In order to opt out of information collection by these companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, please visit:

<http://www.gorillanation.com/privacy/>

<http://www.advertising.com/privacy_policy.php>

<http://www.adonnetwork.com/public/privacy_policy.jsp>

<http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>

**We use cookies for the following reasons:**   
(i) To identify who you are and to access your account information;   
(ii) To estimate our audience size and patterns;   
(iii) To ensure that you are not asked to register twice;   
(iv) To control how often visitors see similar ads;   
(v) To track preferences and to improve and update our Web Sites; and   
(vi) To track the progress and number of entries in some of our promotions and contests. 

Although cookies do identify a user's computer, cookies do not personally identify customers or passwords. Credit card information is not stored in cookies.

**With whom is the information shared?**

**GameReplays.org** will not share, sell or rent your personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information to third party suppliers who provide services on our behalf.

**GameReplays.org** may disclose aggregate statistics about our sales, our Web Sites’ visitors in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

**GameReplays.org may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of GameReplays.org and its Web Sites, visitors to the Web Sites and customers of our Services**.

Our Web Sites contains links to the sites of third parties. When you visit these sites, we suggest that you read their privacy policies. **GameReplays.org** is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites.

We will only sell or rent your personal information to a third party either as part of a sale of the assets of a GameReplays.org company or having ensured that steps have been taken to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

**Security**

**GameReplays.org** places a great importance on the security of all information associated with our customers. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of customer data under our control. For example, our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorised personnel have access to user information. With regard to our Web Sites, we use secure server software (SSL) to encrypt financial information you input before it is sent to us. While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we use our best efforts to prevent this.

**Where is the information stored?**

Information which you submit via our Web Sites is stored on a computer located in the United States of America. This is necessary in order to process the information and to send you any information you have requested. Information submitted by you may be transferred by us to our other offices and to reputable third party suppliers, which may be situated outside the United States of America. Not all countries outside the USA have data protection or privacy laws. In addition, if you use our Services while you are outside the USA, your information may be transferred outside the USA in order to provide you with those Services.

**Specific Services**

By posting information or files on our Web Sites you forfeit your right to ownership of this content and cannot lay any claim to any monies generated either directly or indirectly. This includes all replays, strategies, shoutcasts, videos, VODs, guides, posts, graphics, programmes, executable files, and all other pieces of information, or files, uploaded or posted on our Web Sites.

If you wish to retain your right to ownership of any content or files then you should apply in writing to the Managing Director of **GameReplays.org Limited** and you will be informed of our decision within reasonable time frame.

Users are reminded that chat rooms, forums and areas of the website that allow you to submit content or set up a profile on the website are for public viewing and discussion. Any personal information supplied by users here is widely accessible. **GameReplays.org** is not responsible for the content posted by users of these services. We advise users to be especially careful in such public areas about disclosing personal information such as full name, home address, or phone number

**Web beacons**. Our Web Sites may contain electronic images known as Web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that may be used to assist in delivering or accessing cookies on our sites and allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or our newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

We may also employ Web beacons from third parties in order to help us compile aggregated statistics and determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns. We prohibit Web beacons on our sites from being used by third parties to collect or access your personal information.

Finally, we may work with other companies that advertise on our Web Sites to place Web beacons on their sites in order to allow us to develop statistics on how often clicking on an advertisement on an **GameReplays.org** site results in a purchase or other action on the advertiser's site.
